{
    "educationCourse": {
        "nameOfCourse": "Universe",
        "topics": [
            {
                "topicName": "Solar System",
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "textOfQuestion": "Quantity of planets",
                        "answers": {
                            "answer1": "6",
                            "answer2": "7",
                            "answer3": "8",
                            "answer4": "9"
                        },
                        "correctAnswer": 3
                    },
                    {
                        "textOfQuestion": "Our natural satellite",
                        "answers": {
                            "answer1": "moon",
                            "answer2": "titan",
                            "answer3": "phoenix",
                            "answer4": "num"
                        },
                        "correctAnswer": 1
                    },
                    {
                        "textOfQuestion": "Biggest planet in system",
                        "answers": {
                            "answer1": "earth",
                            "answer2": "jupiter",
                            "answer3": "saturn",
                            "answer4": "neptun"
                        },
                        "correctAnswer": 2
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "topicName": "Galaxies",
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "textOfQuestion": "Name of our galaxy",
                        "answers": {
                            "answer1": "milky way",
                            "answer2": "coffe break",
                            "answer3": "time to tea",
                            "answer4": "claster phoenix"
                        },
                        "correctAnswer": 1
                    },
                    {
                        "textOfQuestion": "Nearest galaxy",
                        "answers": {
                            "answer1": "artemida",
                            "answer2": "claster phoenix",
                            "answer3": "andromeda",
                            "answer4": "stolpy sozidaniya"
                        },
                        "correctAnswer": 3
                    },
                    {
                        "textOfQuestion": "What in center of galaxy",
                        "answers": {
                            "answer1": "orange soda",
                            "answer2": "red line",
                            "answer3": "lost bkb",
                            "answer4": "black hole"
                        },
                        "correctAnswer": 4
                    },
                    {
                        "textOfQuestion": "Form of many galaxies",
                        "answers": {
                            "answer1": "pyramid",
                            "answer2": "spiral",
                            "answer3": "cube",
                            "answer4": "ball"
                        },
                        "correctAnswer": 2
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "topicName": "Planet Earth",
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "textOfQuestion": "How many seas on planet",
                        "answers": {
                            "answer1": "30",
                            "answer2": "40",
                            "answer3": "50",
                            "answer4": "bigger"
                        },
                        "correctAnswer": 4
                    },
                    {
                        "textOfQuestion": "How many mainlands",
                        "answers": {
                            "answer1": "6",
                            "answer2": "7",
                            "answer3": "8",
                            "answer4": "9"
                        },
                        "correctAnswer": 1
                    },
                    {
                        "textOfQuestion": "Biggest mainland",
                        "answers": {
                            "answer1": "north America",
                            "answer2": "Eurasia",
                            "answer3": "Australia",
                            "answer4": "south America"
                        },
                        "correctAnswer": 2
                    },
                    {
                        "textOfQuestion": "Where is Heops pyramid?",
                        "answers": {
                            "answer1": "on Earth",
                            "answer2": "in air",
                            "answer3": "in Giza",
                            "answer4": "under water"
                        },
                        "correctAnswer": 3
                    }
                ]
            }
        ]
    }
}